gigaset.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Gigaset

Gigaset Communications GmbH on the topic of data protection

The protection of personal data is very important to Gigaset Communications GmbH (hereinafter referred to as "Gigaset"). We therefore conduct our activities in compliance with the applicable legal regulations for the protection of personal data and data security. Below, you will find an explanation of the information we collect, how we handle this data and who we make this data available to (if applicable).Personal dataWe do not collect any personal data (e.g., names, addresses, telephone numbers or eMail addresses) via our websites unless this is necessary for contractual purposes or you make this data available to us voluntarily (e.g., during registration, surveys) or the relevant legal regulations regarding the protection of your data permit this data to be collected. 

**Your data is only communicated to third parties if this is necessary for the purpose of contract processing or billing. When an order is processed, we transmit the data required for order, invoice and delivery processing to the service providers that we use (e.g., freight carriers, payment service providers, banks), for example.** **

Purpose

** We generally use the personal data that you make available to us to answer your queries, process your orders or to give you access to specific information or offers. To maintain customer relationships, the following may also be necessary: 

  * We may store and process your personal data to respond to your needs more effectively or to improve our products or services; or 
  * We (or a third party on our behalf) may use this personal data to inform you about product offers that are useful to you or to conduct online surveys to improve our response to the demands and requirements of our customers 

We will not sell your personal data to third parties or market it in any other way. As you would expect, we will respect your wishes if you do not wish to make your personal data available to us to support our customer rela-tionship (in particular, for direct marketing or market research purposes). If this is the case, you can inform us of this at any time as follows:

By contact form at [www.gigaset.com\kontakt](http://www.gigaset.com/ "Opens external link in new window")  
By post: Gigaset Communications GmbH, Hansaallee 299, 40549 Düsseldorf, Germany  
By fax: +49 (0)2871-9163022

 **Intended use  
** Gigaset will collect, process and use the personal data that you make available online solely for the purposes communicated to you, unless collection, processing or use is necessary in the following cases:

  * For a further purpose that is directly connected to the original purpose for which the personal data was collected 
  * To prepare, negotiate and fulfil a contract with you Due to a legal obligation or directive from authorities or legal bodies 
  * To justify or protect legal claims or in defence against complaints 
  * To prevent misuse or other illegal activities, e.g., intentional attacks on the IT systems and to guar-antee data security 

**Security  
** Gigaset undertakes technical and organisational security measures to protect your personal data against unintentional or illegal deletion or modification or against loss, unauthorised forwarding or unauthorised access. 

**Questions and comments  
** Gigaset will respond to all appropriate queries for viewing and, where applicable, correction, addition or deletion of personal data. If you have any questions or comments relating to this privacy policy (for example, regarding viewing and updating your personal data), click "Contact" at the bottom of the screen. We will adjust our privacy policy on an ongoing basis in accordance with further developments of the Internet. We will publicise changes on this page in a timely manner. You should therefore access this page regularly to familiarise yourself with the current version of the privacy policy.

 **Cookies  
** Gigaset's Internet pages use a variety of cookies. They enable us to make our services more user-friendly and more effective. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and that your browser saves. The cookies cannot be assigned to specific persons and do not contain any personal data. This data will not be merged with other sources of data. Most of the cookies that we use are "session cookies", which are deleted when you end your browser session. Cookies do not cause any damage to your computer and do not contain viruses. If you wish to prevent the use of cookies, you can disable cookies in your browser. For details of how to do this for your specific browser, see the instructions from the manufacturer of your browser.

The following cookies are used:  

Cookies Name               | Duration | Brief description  
---|---|---  
Google Analytics| 2 years| Google Analytics is a web ana-lytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics uses "first party" cookies to track visitor interactions. These cookies are used to store information such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page. Browsers do not share first-party cookies across domains.  
Magento Session  
frontend| 

Length of the session

| Session IDs are used to detect multiple related queries from one user and assign them to a session. These sessions often consist of multiple related que-ries and answers. The session ID is transferred by setting ses-sion cookies.  
  
**Newsletters  
** You can subscribe to our newsletter via a link on our homepage. In order to send you the newsletter, we need your eMail address. By giving us your eMail address, you consent to us using your data to send the newsletter in order to inform you about new items in our product portfolio, as well as promotions or general news about Gigaset. The eMail address will only be used to send you the newsletter; it will not be forwarded to third parties. You can unsubscribe from the newsletter and withdraw the consent you have granted for future use at any time. To do this, click on the "Cancel newsletter" button in the newsletter sent to you. Alternatively, go to "Customer services" and "My account" on the Gigaset website and click "Deactivate newsletter".  

**Use of Facebook social plugins  
** Our website uses social plugins ("plugins") provided by the social network facebook.com, operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook"). The plugins are identifiable by a Facebook logo (white letter f on blue background or a thumb up icon) or the notice "Facebook Social Plugin". For a full list of all social plugins please see: <http://developers.facebook.com/plugins.>**  
**  
When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to the Facebook servers. Facebook transmits the content of the plugin directly to your browser and the browser integrates it into the web page. We therefore have no influence on the scope of the data that Facebook collects using this plugin and can only provide the information we currently possess:

The embedded plugins provide Facebook with the information that you have accessed the corresponding page of our website. If you are logged into Facebook, your visit can be assigned to your Facebook account. If you interact with the plugins, for example by clicking "Like", or entering a comment, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to Facebook and stored by it. If you are not a member of Facebook, it is still possible that Facebook may learn and store your IP address.

For further information on the purpose and scope of data collection and further processing and use of the data by Facebook, as well as your corresponding rights and setting options for protecting your privacy, see the Facebook privacy policy: <http://www.facebook.com/policy.php.>

If you are a Facebook member and do not want Facebook to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by Facebook, please log off Facebook before entering our website. 

Further you can block Facebook social Plugins by using add-ons for your browser, like the "Facebook Blocker".

(Template copied from [spreerecht.de/datenschutz/2010-10/das-rechtliche-risiko-bei-facebooks-like-button-inkl-muster-fuer-die-datenschutzerklaerung](http://spreerecht.de/datenschutz/2010-10/das-rechtliche-risiko-bei-facebooks-like-button-inkl-muster-fuer-die-datenschutzerklaerung))

 **Twitter  
** Twitter buttons are integrated on our pages. These buttons are provided by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. These Twitter plugins are recognisable from the terms "Twitter" or "Follow" connected with the Twitter logo (stylised blue bird).

When you access a web page on this website that has a Twitter button, a direct connection is established be-tween your browser and the Twitter server. Twitter transmits the content of the Twitter button directly to your browser. Please be aware that, as the provider of the pages, we have no influence on the scope of data that Twitter collects using these plugins, or on the use of the data collected by Twitter. For more information, see the Twitter privacy policy at [twitter.com/privacy](http://twitter.com/privacy).

 **Google Analytics**  
Our Internet presence uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies" — text files that are stored on your computer and that enable an analysis of your use of the website. The information created by the cookie about your use of this website, such as the time you visited the website as well as the frequency and the action path, is transferred to a Google server and stored there. The server may be outside your country of residence. However, your IP address is automatically truncated, making it anonymous, and is not merged with other data from Google. Due to legal requirements, for example, and for the performance of tasks on behalf of Google (e.g., billing or data storage), the information created can be made available to third parties. In this case, Google will ensure that this data is only processed in compliance with the respective data protection provisions and security measures. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google uses this information to evaluate your use of the website, to create reports about the website activities and to perform further services connected with website use and Internet use for the website operator. You can prevent the cookies being saved via a setting in your browser software. However, please be aware that if you change this setting, you may not be able to use all of the functions of this website to their full extent. By using this website, you are allowing the web analysis service to use your anonymised data. Furthermore, you can prevent Google recording the data created by the cookie and the data relating to your use of the website (incl. your IP address), as well as the processing of this data by Google, by downloading and installing the browser plugin available at the following link: [tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=?&nbsp);

 **Changes to the privacy policy  
** We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time in compliance with the applicable data protection regulations. The current version is dated June 2013.
